Guide to the Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 Records, 1836-1975 AIS.1991.08
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Publications, III.
  - Program Celebrating John Feigel's Twenty-five Years as President by Typographical Union No. 7, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Governor's Study of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Printing and Duplications Facilities by Harris R. Margolis, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Union Propoganda Posters (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 Official Bulletin, 1930-1958 (Microfilm-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Reel 4)
  - Official Bulletin by Local No. 7 (Oversize 3)
  - Pittsburgh Daily Reporter, John Feigel and Typographical Union No. 7 Copies, October 15-November 17, 1950 (Oversize 4-5)
- Finances, IV.
  This series contains the financial records of Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 from 1875 to 1972. Included within the records are dues ledgers dated from 1875 to 1918, records of relief given to workers from 1930 to 1942, and pension reports dated from 1940 to 1953, as well as the 1960s. This series also contains financial records such as Job and Newspaper Chapel books dated from 1911 to 1928. Also present are various financial reports, such as annual reports and the secretary's monthly itemized reports from 1925 to 1970. Cash receipt books and various bank statements from 1954 to 1970 are also included.
  - Dues Ledgers, 1875-1890 (Box 21, Volume 1-4)
  - Cash Index, April 1889- July 1891 (Box 21, Volume 5)
  - Ten Percent Assessment Ledger, 1888-1892 (Box 22, Volume 1-2)
  - Dues Ledgers, 1891-1901 (Box 22, Volume 3-8)
  - Dues Ledgers, 1901-1913 (Box 23, Volume 1-7)
  - Dues Ledgers, 1913-1918 (Box 24, Volume 1-3)
  - Time Books, 1921-1923, 1931 (Box 24, Volume 4-9)
  - Monthly Stamp Reports, 1910-1936 (Box 25, Volume 1-8)
  - Time Book, 1932 (Box 26, Volume 1)
  - International Typo. Union Lessons, 1922-1944 (Box 26, Volume 2-3)
  - Ten Percent Assessment, 1899 and 1906 (Box 26, Volume 4-5)
  - Seven Percent Assessment, 1906-1907 (Box 26, Volume 6)
  - Two Percent Assessment, 1907-1908 (Box 26, Volume 7)
  - One Percent Assessment, 1907 (Box 26, Volume 8)
  - Three Percent Assessment (Box 26, Volume 9)
  - One Half Percent Assessment, 1908 (Box 26, Volume 10)
  - Job Chapel, 1911-1912 (Box 26, Volume 11)
  - Per Capita and Dues, 1912-1914 (Box 26, Volume 12)
  - Job Office and Dues, 1914-1916 (Box 26, Volume 13)
  - Newspaper Chapel, 1914-1916 (Box 26, Volume 14)
  - Job Chapels, 1917-1921 (Box 26, Volume 15)
  - Newspaper Chapels, 1917-1920 (Box 26, Volume 16)
  - Job Chapels, 1921-1923 (Box 27, Volume 1)
  - Newspaper Chapels, 1920-1923 (Box 27, Volume 2)
  - Job Chapels, 1921-1928 (Box 27, Volume 3-4)
  - Newspaper Chapels, 1924-1928 (Box 27, Volume 5)
  - Pittsburgh Typographical Union Financial Reports, 1925-1926 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Secretary's Financial Reports, 1927-1933 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Summary of Cash Reciepts, 1926-1927 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Financial Reports, 1928-1931 (Box 27, Folder 4-7)
  - Chapels, 1931-1932 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Finances, 1932-1933 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper and Secretary's Chapels, 1933-1934 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Summary of Cash Dispersments, 1930-1942 (Box 27, Volume 6)
  - Copy's of Bonds from the Fidelity and Casuality Company of New York, 1932-1949 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Financial Records, 1933-1943 (Box 28, Volume 1)
  - Expenses of Entertainment Committee, 1941 (Box 28, Volume 2)
  - Financial Records, 1936-1942 (Box 28, Volume 3)
  - Check Stubs for a Special Fund of No. 7, 1937-1944 (Box 28, Volume 4)
  - Relief Check Stubs, 1930-1934 (Box 28, Volume 5-12)
  - Relief Check Stubs, 1934-1942 (Box 29, Volume 1-4)
  - Relief Roll, 1932-1935 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Relief Record, 1932-1942 (Box 29, Volume 5)
  - Financial Records, 1943-1947 (Box 29, Volume 6)
  - Pension Requisitions and Roll Reports, 1940-1944 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Financial Reports, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Pension Requisitions and Roll Reports, 1945-1949 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records, 1948-1950 (Box 29, Folder 5-7)
  - Pension Requisistions and Roll Reports, 1950-1953 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Cash Reciepts, 1938-1946 (Box 30, Volume 1)
  - Finances, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records, 1952-1954 (Box 31, Folder 2-4)
  - Secretary's Monthly Itemized Reports, 1950-1955 (Box 31, Volume 1-2)
  - Financial Reports, 1955-1958 (Box 32, Folder 1-4)
  - Pittsburgh Union Label Council Finances in Mellon Bank and Trust, 1951-1958 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Statements of Pension Trust Account, 1959-1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Secretary's Monthly Itemized Reports, March 1960 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Pension Roll Report, 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Financial Reports, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Secretary's Monthly Itemized Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 32, Volume 1)
  - Petty Cash Account Book, 1955-1973 (Box 32, Volume 2-4)
  - Cash Reciepts, 1954-1963 (Box 33, Volume 1)
  - Cash Reciepts, 1963-1967 (Box 34, Volume 1)
  - Secretary's Monthly Itemized Report, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Volume 1)
  - Financial Reports, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Minor and Secretary's Chapels, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Financial Reports, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Pension Roll Report, 1963-1969 (Box 35, Folder 4-10)
  - Secretary's Monthly Itemized Reports, January 1969- December 1970 (Box 35, Folder 11-21)
  - Typo Two Phase-Out Pension Plan, 1970 (Box 36, Volume 1)
  - Review of Pension Plan Investments, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - I.T.U. Negotiated Pension Plan, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 2-7)
  - Secretary's Monthly Itemized Reports, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 8-13)
  - Financial Discrepency, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Errors on Monthly Itemized Reports, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Dues Ledgers, 1891-1895 (Oversize 6-7)
  - Cash Receipts and Dues Ledger, 1950s (Oversize 8)
  - Typographical Union No. 7 Poster: "On Strike Against Daily Messenger", 1. (Map-case 3, Drawer 12)
  - Typographical Union No. 7 Blank "On Strike" Posters, 2-4.
- Membership, V.
  This series contains membership records and information of Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7. Included are membership roll books with annual membership and monthly dues lists from 1927 to 1949. Also included are records of members suspended or expelled from local union No. 7, as well as those blacklisted from the years 1884 to 1889. This series also contains membership applications and applications to receive mortuary benefits from the years 1915 to 1944. Lists of members receiving a pension from 1922 to 1937 are also included.
  - List of Officers and Members in Good Standing, 1868 (Map-case 3, Folder 16)
  - Suspension and Expulsion List, 1884-1908 (Map-case 3, Volume 2)
  - Black List or "Rat Book", 1899 (Map-case 3, Volume 3)
  - Printers Assembly and Union No. 7 Working Cards, 1880-1923 (Map-case 3, Item 1)
  - Admitted to Membership, 1926-1928 (Map-case 3, Volume 4)
  - Membership Roll Book, 1927-1932 (Map-case 3, Volume 5)
  - Applications for Membership, 1915-1919 (Map-case 3, Folder 17-19)
  - Applications for Membership, 1919-1937 (Box 37, Folder 1-6)
  - Membership Applications (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Apprenticeship Standards for Application to Membership, 1938-1944 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Applications for Mortuary Benefits, 1915-1944 (Box 37, Folder 9-12)
  - Old Age Pension Rolls, 1922-1937 (Box 37, Volume 1-7)
  - Rollbook for Union Label Council, 1932-1949 (Box 37, Volume 8)
  - Members' Traveling Cards, 1925-1940 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Information for Members of Typo. Union No. 7, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Apprenticeship Applications from the Department of Labor and Industry, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Edward S. Cook Dues and Membership Cards, 1882-1923 (Oversize 9)
  - List of Apprentices, 1944, 1947; 5-7. (Map-case 3, Drawer 12)
- Contracts and Arbitration, VI.
  This series contains contract negotiations and proposals, as well as signed and approved contracts between Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 and other organizations such as the Pittsburgh Courier, the Pittsburgh Newspaper Publishers' Association, and the Union Employing Printers Association of Pittsburgh from 1914 to 1970. The contracts between Pittsburgh No. 7 and its members are also contained within this series along with price, wage, and newspaper scales used in contract negotiations from the years 1836 to 1956. This series contains arbitration matters involving Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 and other parties such as members of No. 7, the organizations that have entered into contract agreements with No. 7, and the Joint Union Committee from the years 1901 to 1968. Case briefs, rebuttals, and rebuttal briefs are also included.
  - List of Prices Adopted by Journeymen Printers of Pittsburgh, 1836 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Constitution, Bylaws, and Rules of Order of Local No. 7, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Price Scales, 1899 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Appeal of 1901 Ordinance (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Agreement Between Newspaper Publishers' Association of Pittsburgh and Local No. 7, 1914-1919 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Contracts and Agreements, 1918-1919 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Agreement Between the Providence Journal Company and the Providence Typographical Union, November 1919 -October 1920 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Agreement Between the Pittsburgh Publishers' Association and Local No. 7, 1920 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Agreement Between the Pittsburgh Publishers' Association and Local No. 7, 1919-1921 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Supplemental Agreement of the Pittsburgh Publishers' Asscoiation and Local no. 7, 1919-1921 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Agreement on Wage Scale, 1921 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Scale, January 1922- January 1923 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Appeal of Frank A. Schroder v. Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7, June 1923 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Charges of Violation of Obligations; Peter A. Grimes v. Charles Connolly, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Minimum Wage Scales of Typographical Unions, May 31, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Report of Testimony, June 17, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Scale, Januaury 1924- January 1926 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Amendment to the International Typographical Union Bylaws, 1927 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Agreement Between Pittsburgh Publishers' Association and Local No. 7, January 1928- January 1931 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Minimum Wage Scales of Typogrpahical Unions, May 31, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Working Agreement Between Signer, Herbrick, and Held, 1929 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Group Insurance Agreement, 1929 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Decision on Holiday Overtime, 1929-1930 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Hampsey Appeal, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Appeal of C.H. McMannemon, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Eugene Merz Appeal in Discharge Case, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Press Management v. Leidigh and Liston, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Proposition for a Five-Day Work Week, 1930-1931 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Agreement Between Pittsburgh Newspaper Publishers' Association and Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7, July 1929- January 1931 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Statement of Dispute Between Taxi Cab Drivers and Cab Company, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - C.H. Britton Case, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Walter Raab Discharge Case, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Dispute Involving the Interpretation of the Typographical Contract, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - McCormick Appeal Case, 1931-1932 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Appeal to Pennsylvania State Legislature, 1931-1932 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Minimum Wage Scales of Typographical Unions, 1931-1932 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Watkins Appeal on Two Percent Assessment, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Herbrick and Held Chapel Wage Cut Proposed, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Ross Humphrey Jr. Case, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Agreement Between Pittsburgh Newspaper Publishers' Association and Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7, 1932-1933 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Edward Kruckewitt Appeal, 1932-1933 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Negotiations and Agreement Concerning a Five-Day Week, 1932-1933 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Supplemental Agreement to a Five-Day Week, January 1933 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Funeral Directors v. Grigsby, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Proposed Newspaper Contract Not Approved by the I.T.U., 1929-1934 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Regulations for Benefits and Relief Data, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Callback Appeal of the Press Chapel, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Rules Governing Extra Work, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Arbitration of Newspaper Wage Scales, 1934-1936 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Gal 1-7 Scale, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Joe Cross Case, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - National Industrial Recovery Act, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - Minimum Wage Scales of Typographical Unions, 1934-1935 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Transcript of Testimony in H.L. Woodmansee v. Charles Wolf, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 54-57)
  - Transcript of Testimony in H.L. Woodmansee v. Charles Wolf, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
  - An Appeal to the Membership of Typographical Union No. 7, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Decision of the Joint Union Committee in the Case of Pittsburgh Publishers' Association and Local No. 7, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Brief of Typographical Union No. 7, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - International Typographical Union Brief Submitted to the President of the United States, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Scale, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Dispute Between Pittsburgh Publishers' Association and Local No. 7, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Wage Arbitration Matters, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Brief on Typo. Union No. 7 in the case of Typo Union No. 7 and Pittsburgh Publishers' Association, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Rebuttal Brief of Pittsburgh Typo. Union No. 7, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Hearing, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Pittsburgh Publishers' Association Brief, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Proceedings in Pittsburgh Publishers' Association and Pittsburgh Typo. Union No. 7, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Transcript of Proceedings in Pittsburgh Newspaper Publishers' Association and Pittsburgh Typo. Union No. 7, 1936-1937 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Minimum Wage Scales of Typographical Unions, 1936-1937 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Agreement Between Pittsburgh Newspaper Publishers' Association and Pittsburgh Typo. Union No. 7, 1936-1937 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Contract Terms, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Joint Standing Committee Recommendations, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Scale Proposals, 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Publishers' Case-in-Chief First Edition, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Publishers' Case-in-Chief Second Edition, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Publisher's Rebuttal to the Brief of the Joint Union Committee, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - The Board of Arbitration, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Brief of the Joint Union Committee, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 26-29)
  - Rebuttal Brief of the Joint Union Committee, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 30-33)
  - Statement of Thomas C. Langdon and Charles E. Herman, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Rebuttal Brief of Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Minimum Wage Scales of Typographical Unions, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Revisions to Agreement and Scale of Wages, April 1, 1938 - March 31, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Agreement and Scale of Wages Between Union Employing Printers' Association of Pittsburgh and Typo. Union No. 7, 1938-1939 (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
  - Record of Proceedings in the Case of Typographical Union No. 7 and Pittsburgh Newspaper Publishers' Association, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Typographical Contract, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Decisions on Newspaper Scale, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Agreement and Scale of Wages, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Reply to Brief and Sur-Rebuattal Brief in case of Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 v. Andrew Mervick, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Pittsburgh Newspaper Guild Contract, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Meeting of the Board of Arbitration in the Matter of Wages Only, June 1939 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Report of the Chairman of the Board of Arbitration, June 1939 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Case of Victor Schoppelery v. Pittsburgh Typo. Union No. 7, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Typographical Contract, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Book of Laws Agreed Upon by Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7, January 1, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Supplemental Agreement Between the Braddock Free Press and the Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Scale Negotiations, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Agreement and Scale of Wages Between Union Employing Printers' Association and Typo. Union No. 7, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Supplemental Agreement, July 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Agreement and Scale of Wages Between Union Employing Printers' Association of Pittsburgh and Typo. Union No. 7, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Complete Briefs of WM. J. Wise and Pittsburgh Typo. Union in Appeal to I.T.U. Executive Council, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Complete Briefs of Appeal in Charles J. Mack v. Pittsburgh Typo. Union No. 7, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Signed Contract Between Union Employing Printers' Association of Pittsburgh and Typo. Union No. 7, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Minimum Wage Scales of Typographical Unions, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Agreement and Scale of Wages Between Union Employing Printers' Association and Typo. Union No. 7, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Contract Approved by the International Typographical Union, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Book and Job Scale, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Scale Contract, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Typographical Contract, July 1941 - December 1942 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Contract Negotiations Between Typo. No. 7 and the Pittsburgh Courier, 1941-1942 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Scale of Wages, 1941-1942 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Job Scale Negotiations, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Appeal of George Ballinger v. Pittsburgh Typo. Union No. 7, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Meadville Typographical Union No. 181 v. The Tribune Publishing Company, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Appeal of Harold Blumer v. Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Local Arbitration Board in The Greensburg-Jeanette Typographical Union No. 668, 1942-1943 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - R.T. Lewis Co. Contract; Nullified, 1942-1943 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Minimum Wage Scales of Typographical Unions, 1942-1943 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Negotiations, Newspaper Scale, and Proposed Contract of Typo. Union No. 7, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Job Scale for Non-members of Employers Association, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Signed Contract Between American Slav Printing Association and Typo. Union No. 7, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Brief in Behalf of the Employers in case of Typo. Union No. 7 and Union Employing Printers' Association of Pittsburgh, April 15, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Employers Brief and Rebuttal in case of Typo. Union No. 7 and Union Employing Printers' Association of Pittsburgh, April 26, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Rebuttal Brief of Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 in case of Typo. Union No. 7 and Union Employing Printers' Association of Pittsburgh, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Direct Brief of Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 in case of Typo. Union No. 7 and Union Employing Printers' Association of Pittsburgh, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Pittsburgh Courier WLB Petition, 1943 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Signed Courier Contract, 1943 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Negotiations Between Pittsburgh Typo Union No. 7 and Pittsburgh Newspapers, 1943-1944 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - News Negotiations, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Minimum Wage Scale Pamphlets, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Job Contract and Newspaper Scale Data, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Signed Contract of the Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Appeal of Ronald C. Knepper v. Typographical Union No. 7, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - First Contract Signed by Steel Publications Inc., November 8, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - First Signed Contract with Pittsburgh Typo. No. 7 by William G. Johnston Printing Co., December 11. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Signed Courier Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Data, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Job Negotiations, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Negotiations, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Signed Newspaper Agreement, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Standards of Apprenticeship for the Printing Trade, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Westinghouse Valley Printing Company v. I.T.U. and Typo. Union No. 7, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Minimum Wage Scale Pamphlets, 1945-1946 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration Dispute Over Interpreting the Contract, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Job Scale Data, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Printing Industry Agreements, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Dispute Between Typo. Union No. 7 and the Pittsburgh Press, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Complete Case of Charles J. Mack v. Typographical Union No. 7, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Proposed Commercial Contract and Job Scale, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Commercial Agreement Between Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 and Union Employing Printers' Association of Pittsburgh, November 1945-April 1947 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Scale, 1946-1947 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Agreement Between the Pittsburgh Courier and Pittsburgh Typogrpahical Union No. 7, March 1946-February 1947 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Taft-Hartley Regulations, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Present and Proposed Agreement Between Pittsburgh Newspaper Publishers' Association and Typographical Union No. 7, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Contract Provisions which May be Proposed According to the National Labor Relations Board, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - United States of America Before the National Labor Realtions Board, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - An Appeal Against a Mandated Contract, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - An Appeal to the 89th Cleveland Convention, August 1947 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - National Labor Relations Board Charge Against One of their Agents, October 7, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Pittsburgh Typographical Contract, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Job Scale and Commercial Agreement Between the Union Printers' Section of Pittsburgh and Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Agreement Between the Pittsburgh Courier and Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7, March 1947-1948 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Minimum Wage Scale Pamphlets, 1947-1948 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Pittsburgh Typographical Contract, 1947-1948 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Apprenticeship Standards and Agreement, 1945-1949 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Press Suspension, July 30-31, 1949 and August 1-2, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Proposed Agreement Between Pittsburgh Publishers' Association and Pittsburgh Typo. No. 7, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Proposal, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Agreement Between Pittsburgh Typo. No. 7 and Union Employers Printing Section of Pittsburgh, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Agreement, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Minimum Wage Scale Pamphlets, 1949-1950 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Agreement, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Agreement, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Signed Job Contract, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Appeal Taken by Stephen J. Flaherty, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Unsigned Contract, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Signed Contract Between Pittsburgh Typo. No. 7 and the Pittsburgh Courier, 1950-1951 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - National Labor Relations Board Case, 1950-1951 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Minimum Wage Scale Pamphlets, 1951-1952 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Proposed Contract of Pittsburgh Typo. Union No. 7, 1951-1953 (Box 42, Folder 14)